<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vi Le</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Vi Le</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dipping My Toes into Python</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/08/dipping-my-toes-into-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/08/dipping-my-toes-into-python/</guid>
      <description>Python, it was a language I never knew I loved, and here&#39;s why: We started python in class pretty late. I was excited to learn a new language because I hear all these great things about how it is simpler than R. It was very easy to use and the format was easy to understand. Using the servers probably helped with that since everything was already uploaded for us. The two languages paired so well with one another, the complementation was much needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>food bloggy</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/04/bloggy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/04/bloggy/</guid>
      <description>This was how my Thanksgiving looked like! A cranberry citrus tart, recipe was from Claire Saffitz. Peaches from my mom&#39;s tree were turned into this beautiful peach crumble bar These are my crispy chocolate chip cookies I made a dinner celebrating my first real apartment for my family. I made roasted garlic mashed potatoes, american wagyu ribeye, mallard duck breast, A5 miyazaki wagyu, broccolini and campari tomatoes! I made &#39;cwispy&#39; fried chicken for my dad&#39;s birthday!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Vi Le vtl269  Introduction: The two datasets that I have chosen are MathAchSchool and MathAchieve. The MathAchieve data was acquired by Steve Walker and the MathAchSchool data was made to accompany the MathAch data. I chose these two datasets because I wanted to see the data and the variables that went into it. In the MathAch data, the varaibles are school (school ID) , minority (yes or no factor), sex (male or female), SES (a numerical vector on how many socioeconomic statuses the student faces), MathAch (a numeric vector of mathematics achievement scores) and MEANSES (a numeric vector of the mean SES for the school).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Vi Le vtl269  Introduction: The data I chose to use is called &amp;quot;CASchools&amp;quot;. This data set includes 420 observations from K-6 and K-8 districts in California and 14 variables. The variables are the following: district (district code), school (school name), county (a factor indicating county), grades (factor that indicates grade span of district), student (shows the total enrollment), teachers (number of teachers), calworks (percentage of those who qualify for income assistance), lunch (percentage of those who qualify for reduced lunch), computer (number of computers), expenditure (spending per student), income (average income for district), english (percent of English learners), read (average reading score) and math (average math score).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description> VI LE Email: t.vile00@utexas.edu  Education The University of Texas at Austin BSA in Biology | 2021  Pre-Health Professions Certificate    Skills  Good at loving my dogs Doing this project in a timely manner   Interests  Baking and cooking Taking photos of my creations   Lab Experience Isotope Geochemistry Lab Assistant  Performed the chemistry that was needed for the samples collected Detail-oriented with the equipment that was used    Work Experience Team Member at Target  Guest services Produce trained Expert Specialty Sales    Accomplishments  Houston Livestock Show &amp;amp; Rodeo Scholar Recipient of the Anna Mae Hutchison Endowed Scholarship Award    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume1/</guid>
      <description> VI LE  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
